They will tell you that more police will make you safer, but not that more resources will make people less inclined to do crime.
They will tell you that TSA will make you safer, not that the threat of violence is a result of America creating violence globally.
They're protecting the people they answer to from you.
These are all the cop city locations currently planned.
It's not just Atlanta, Georgia, is it?
Some would say we're looking at a cop nation project.
Now look at Washington state.
Why more locations than other states?
If you see these locations as prep sites to stomp uprisings and know our state's history of resistance, it makes a lot of sense.
Stop Cop City.
Stop City.